Guide to the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America records, 1914-1980.
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America records, 1914-1980.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America records, 1914-1980, 1920-1950 (bulk)
5619
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America.
207.5 linear ft.
Correspondence, clippings, minutes, organizing leaflets, photographs, speeches, phonographs, scrapbooks, and organizational records.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, clippings, minutes, organizing leaflets, photographs, speeches, phonographs, scrapbooks, and organizational records documenting the founding, growth, history and development of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; the activities of its officers and other leading officials; its organizing activities; and its administration.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the most significant union representing workers in the men's clothing industry, was founded in Chicago in 1914 as a breakaway movement from the United Garment Workers.
Under the leadership of Sidney Hillman, the ACWA grew rapidly. By the late 1920s the union had organized over 100,000 members in the major garment industry cities across the United States and Canada. The depression severely thinned its ranks, but by the mid-1930s, the union had regained sufficient organizational strength to become a leading player in the creation of the CIO.
Sidney Hillman became an influential figure in political circles and a key advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt on labor and economic issues, serving on the board of the National Recovery Administration. During World War II, Hillman was named associate director of the Office of Production Management, which assisted in mobilizing the nation's resources for the war effort.
Hillman's death in 1946 was a significant blow to the ACWA. Though the union continued to grow under his successor, Jacob Potofsky, its influence in national political and labor affairs was diminished. In 1976, the union merged with the Textile Workers of America to become the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; In 1995 the ACTWU voted to merge with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union to form the Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE).
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, clippings, minutes, organizing leaflets, photographs, speeches, phonographs, scrapbooks, and organizational records documenting the founding, growth, history and development of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; the activities of its officers and other leading officials; its organizing activities; and its administration.
Significant individuals represented in the collection include Sidney Hillman, Joseph Schlossberg, Jacob Potofsky, Dorothy Jacobs Bellanca, E.J. Brais, Bessie Hillman, and August Bellanca.
Among the topics covered in the collection are the men's garment industry in the U.S. and Canada; union organizing, collective bargaining, strikes and other labor disputes in both countries; records of local unions; working conditions in the U.S. garment industry; union management, finances, and legal matters; the New Deal, particularly Sidney Hillman's involvement in the National Recovery Administration; and economic mobilization during World War II, including Hillman's records from his service with the National Defense Advisory Commission and the War Production Board.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America.; Addams, Jane, 1860-1935.; Addes, George F., 1910-; Anderson, Mary, 1872-1964.; Antonini, Luigi, 1883-1968.; Andrews, John B. (John Bertram), 1880-1943.; Bellanca, August.; Bellanca, Dorothy.; Berry, George Leonard, 1882-1948.; Blinken, S. M.; Blumberg, Hyman, 1885-1968.; Brais, E. J.; Brandeis, Louis Dembitz, 1856-1941.; Bridges, Harry, 1901-; Brophy, John, 1883-1963.; Cohn, Fannia M. (Fannia Mary), 1885-; Danish, Max D.; Darrow, Clarence, 1857-1938.; Dewey, Thomas E. (Thomas Edmund), 1902-1971.; Dickason, Gladys.; Dubinsky, David, 1892-; Frankfurter, Felix, 1882-1965.; Giovannitti, Arturo M., 1884-1959.; Green, Henry.; Green, William, 1872-1952.; Hardman, J. B. S. (Jacob Benjamin Salutsky), 1882-1968.; Hellman, Lillian, 1906-; Hendley, Charles J.; Hillman, Bessie.; Hillman, Sidney, 1887-1946.; Hollander, Louis, b. 1893.; Kallen, Horace Meyer, 1882-1974.; Kellogg, Paul Underwood, 1879-1958.; Knudsen, William S., 1879-1948.; La Follette, Philip Fox, 1897-1965.; La Follette, Robert M. (Robert Marion), 1895-1953.; La Guardia, Fiorello H. (Fiorello Henry), 1882-1947.; Lehman, Herbert H. (Herbert Henry), 1878-1963.; Lewis, John Llewellyn, 1880-1969.; Lewis, Sinclair, 1885-1951.; Lovestone, Jay.; Martin, Warren Homer, 1902-1968.; Mason, Lucy Randolph, 1882-1959.; Mooney, Thomas J., 1882-1942.; Niebuhr, Reinhold, 1892-1971.; Morrison, Frank, 1859-1949.; Muste, Abraham John, 1885-1967.; Perkins, Frances, 1880-1965.; Poletti, Charles.; Potofsky, Jacob S. (Jacob Samuel), 1894-1979.; Pressman, Lee, 1906-; Reuther, Walter, 1907-1970.; Rieve, Emil, 1892-1975.; Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962.; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945.; White, Walter Francis, 1893-1955.; Rosenblum, Frank, 1888-1973.; Schaffner, Joseph, 1848-1918.; Schlossberg, Joseph, 1875-1971.; Schneiderman, Rose, 1882-; Seidman, Joel Isaac, 1906-; Sinclair, Upton, 1878-1968.; Truman, Harry S., 1884-1972.; Vladeck, B. (Baruch Charney), 1886-1935.; Wagner, Robert F. (Robert Ferdinand), 1877-1953.; Wallace, Henry Agard, 1888-1965.; Williams, John E.; Woll, Matthew, 1880-1956.; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America--Administration.; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America--Finance.; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America--Presidents.; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Women's Dept.; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Women's Dept.--Officials and employees.; American Clothing Manufacturers of New York.; American Federation of Labor.; American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee.; American League Against War and Fascism.; Brookwood Labor College (Katonah, N.Y.); Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.); Consumers' League of New York City.; Hart, Schaffner & Marx.; Hart, Schaffner & Marx--Employees.; Hickey Freeman and Company.; Industrial Workers of the World.; International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada.; International Union, United Automobile Workers of America (CIO); Journeymen Tailors of America.; Journeymen Tailors of America--Officials and employees.; Kuppenheimer and Company.; Labor's Non-Partisan League.; Mooney Molders Defense Committee.; Nash Clothing Company.; Nash Clothing Company--Employees.; National Association for the Advancement of Colored People.; National Consumers' League.; National Urban League.; Plumb Plan League (Washington, D.C.); Socialist Party (U.S.); Steel Workers Organizing Committee (U.S.); Textile Workers Organizing Committee; Textile Workers Union of America.; United Garment Workers of America.; United States.Army--Procurement.; United States. Commission on Industrial Relations.; United States. Dept. of Labor.; United States. National Defense Advisory Commission.; United States. National Defense Advisory Commission--Officials and employees.; United States. National Recovery Administration.; United States. National Recovery Administration--Officials and employees.; United States. National War Labor Board (1918-1919); United States. Navy--Procurement.; United States. War Dept.; United States. War Production Board.; United States. War Production Board--Officials and employees.; United States.--Womens' Bureau.; Women's Trade Union League of America.; Workmen's Circle/Arbeter Ring.
Subjects:
Arbitration, Industrial--United States.; Clothing workers--Health and hygiene--Illinois--Chicago.; Clothing workers--Health and hygiene--United States.; Clothing workers--Labor unions--Canada.; Clothing workers--Labor unions--Organizing--Canada.; Clothing workers--Labor unions--Organizing--Massachusetts--Boston.; Clothing workers--Labor unions--Organizing--New York (State)--Rochester.; Clothing workers--Labor unions--Organizing--Ohio--Cincinnati.; Clothing workers--Labor unions--Organizing--Ontario--Toronto.; Clothing workers--Labor unions--Organizing--Pennsylvania--Philadelphia.; Clothing workers--Labor unions--Organizing--Québec (Province)--Montréal.; Clothing workers--Labor unions--Organizing--United States.; Clothing workers--Labor unions--United States.; Collective bargaining--Clothing industry--Canada.; Collective bargaining--Clothing industry--United States.; Ethnic relations--Canada.; Ethnic relations--United States.; Industrial mobilization--United States.; Labor disputes--United States.; Labor policy--United States.; Labor union locals.; Men's clothing industry--Canada.; Men's clothing industry--Illinois.; Men's clothing industry--New York (State)--New York.; Men's clothing industry--Ohio--Cincinnati.; Men's clothing industry--United States.; New Deal, 1933-1939.; Strikes and lockouts--Clothing trade--United States.; Strikes and lockouts--Clothing workers--Canada.; Strikes and lockouts--Clothing workers--Ohio--Cincinnati.; Strikes and lockouts--Clothing workers--United States.; Strikes and lockouts--United States.; Tailors--Labor unions--United States.; Tailors--Labor unions--Organizing--United States.; Tailors--Labor unions--Canada.; Tailors--Labor unions--Organizing--Canada.; Unemployment--New York (State)--New York.; Unemployed--New York (State)--New York.; Women clothing workers--Labor unions--United States.; Women clothing workers--Labor unions--Organizing--United States.; Women labor union members--United States.; Work environment--Illinois--Chicago.; Work environment--United States.; World War, 1914-1918--Economic aspects--United States.
Places:
Canada--Ethnic relations.; New York (N.Y.)--Economic conditions.; United States--Economic conditions--1918-1945.; United States--Economic policy--1933-1945.; United States--Ethnic relations.
Titles:
Forverts.; Nation (New York, N.Y.: 1865)
Form and Genre Terms:
Correspondence; Minutes; Leaflets; Clippings; Ephemera; Photographs; Phonograph records; Scrapbooks; Administrative records; Speeches
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Restrictions on Access:
Access to some portions of the collection is restricted; contact Kheel Center reference archivist for further details.
RELATED MATERIAL
5107 Hart, Schaffner & Marx, Chicago Industrial Federation of Clothing Manufacturers, United Garment Workers and the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America Board of Arbitration and the Trade Board: decisions of the Boards, 1913-1925.
5108. Rochester (NY) Clothiers Exchange and Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Rochester Joint Board, cases 1-2208: arbitration files, 1919-1926.
5110. Jacob Billikopf arbitration awards for the New York men's clothing industry, 1925-1927.
5273. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Rochester Joint Board minutes, 1919-1966
5285 mf. Sidney Hillman. Scrapbook, 1930-1951.
5287. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Rochester Joint Board, 1964-1976.
5305. Benjamin H. Wolf arbitration papers, 1952-1975.
5619 A. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Agreements.
5619 AA. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Contract files.
5619 AV. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Audio-visual collection.
5619 B. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Additional files.
5619 C. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union.
5619 mb. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Memorabilia.
5619 mf. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Microfilm, 1911-1961.
5619 OH. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Oral history.
5665 mf. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Fall River Local. Minute Books, 1949-1977.
5670. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Ida Alter. Organizer's Diary, 1937-1938.
5674 tr. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Interviews.
5743. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Photographs.
5744. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. J.P. Stevens boycott. Clippings.
5868 mf. Joseph Schlossberg. Diaries and scrapbooks.
5973 m. Joint Board of Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America and New York Cloting Manufacturing Exchange, Inc. Agreement, 1924.
5993. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Rochester Joint Board. Minutes, 1919-1932.
6015. Hyman Blumberg. Records and Memorabilia.
6015 P. Hyman Blumberg. Photographs.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
I. Sidney Hillman correspondence, 1911-1929.
Boxes 1-7
II. Joseph Schlossberg correspondence, 1914-1929.
Boxes 8-17
III. Jacob Potofsky correspondence, 1913-1929.
Boxes 18-27
IV. Dorothy Jacobs Bellanca papers, 1914-1946.
A. Organizing correspondence.
Boxes 28-32
B. General correspondence.
Boxes 33-35
C. Miscellanous correspondence.
Box 35
V. E.J. Brais correspondence, 1915.
Boxes 36-37
VI. Records of joint boards and local unions, 1914-1970.
A. Records of joint boards and local unions, 1914-1930.
Boxes 37-45
B. Papers of joint boards and local unions, 1914-1930.
Boxes 45A-56
C. Records of joint boards and local unions, 1931-1970.
Boxes 57-64
D. General correspondence file, 1913-1941, and charter applications from locals.
Box 65
VII. Sidney Hillman papers, 1930-1946.
A. Correspondence, 1930-46.
Boxes 66-92
B. National Industry Recovery Administration records, 1934-1946.
Boxes 93-99
C. National Defense Advisory Commission records
Box 100
D. War Production Board records.
Boxes 100-111
VIII. Executive officers' papers, 1914-1971.
A. Bessie Hillman correspondence, 1930-1970.
Boxes 112-120
B. Jacob Potofsky. Assistant President and Secretary-Treasurer's correspondence, 1930-1946.
Boxes 121-128
C. Jacob Potofsky presidential correspondence, 1946-1974.
Boxes 129-134
D. Joseph Schlossberg correspondence, 1930-1940.
Boxes 135-145
E. Abt, John. General Counsel's correspondence, 1938-1947.
Box 146
F. August Bellanca. General Organizer's correspondence, 1914-1953.
Box 146
G. Benjamin, Sidney. Assistant Secretary-Treasurer, 1945-1966.
Box 146
H. Bisno, Beatrice. Secretary to Sidney Hillman. Correspondence, 1920-1927.
Box 146
I. Blumberg, Hyman. 1916-1947.
Boxes 147-148
J. Sol Brandzel. Assistant General Secretary-Treasurer, 1961-1969.
Box 149
K. Alex Cohen. Manager, Shirt Workers Joint Board. 1935-1940.
Box 149
L. Tecia Davidson. Secretary to Sidney Hillman, 1938-1941
Box 149
M. Gladys Dickason. Director, Research Department. 1935-1945.
Box 149
N. Charles W. Ervin. 1925-1948
Box 150
O. J. B. S. Hardman. Editor, Advance. 1925-1941.
Box 150
P. Abraham Hershkowitz. Representative, 1938.
Box 150
Q. Louis Hollander. Co-Manager, New York Joint Board, 1936-1938.
Box 150
R. Leo Krzycki. Organizer, 1935-1939.
Box 150
S. Fred Reinfold. Auditing Department. Financial reports, 1945.
Box 150
T. Richard Rohman. Research Department. 1947-1952.
Box 150
U. Frank Rosenblum. 1914-1969.
Boxes 150-152
V. Lester Rosner. Correspondence, 1940.
Box 152
W. Samuel Howard. Assistant President, 1966-1969.
Box 152
X. Jacob Sheinkman. General Counsel and Secretary-Treasurer. 1966, 1972.
Box 152
Y. Valentin Wertheimer. Assistant Secretary-Treasurer, 1954-1974.
Box 152
Z. ACWA Summer School (1962-1971)
Boxes 153-155
IX. Personal papers.
A. Sidney Hillman.
Boxes 156-159
B. Bessie Hillman.
Box 160
C. Jacob Potofsky.
Boxes 161-163
X. General executive board minutes.
A. Minutes.
Boxes 164-167
B. General Executive Board Resolutions
Boxes 167-168
C. Jacob Potofsky's Notes on General Executive Board meetings
Box 168
XI. Speeches and writings.
A. Sidney Hillman, 1914-46.
Boxes 169-171
B. Jacob Potofsky. Speeches and Writings. 1918-72.
Boxes 172-188
C. Speeches and writings by various authors.
Box 189
XII. Press releases.
Boxes 190-191
XIII. Financial and legal records.
A. Financial records.
Boxes 192-194
B. Legal papers.
Boxes 195-197
XIV. Miscellaneous documents.
Boxes 198-225
XV. Departmental records.
A. Department of Cultural Affairs.
Box 226
B. Finance Department
Box 227
C. Research Department
Boxes 228-270
XVI. Contracts.
Boxes 271-283
XVII. Printed and pamphlet materials.
A. Organizing leaflets, 1915-1975.
Boxes 284-288
B. ACWA Local union and joint board histories.
Boxes 289-290
C. ACWA Publications.
Boxes 291-293
XVIII. Clippings.
Boxes 298-311
XIX. Audio-visual materials.
A.Phonograph records.
Box 312
B. Photographs.
Box 313-318
XX. Amalgamated scrapbooks.
XXI. Miscellaneous scrapbooks.
CONTAINER LIST
- I. Sidney Hillman correspondence, 1911-1929. (Box 1-7)
  Correspondence primarily documenting Sidney Hillman's activities as the ACWA's first president during its formative years. Early correspondence with such figures as Joseph Schlossberg and Jacob Potofsky describes the 1914 split with the United Garment Workers, which led to the formation of the ACWA. Letters from Potofsky, E.J. Brais and Frank Rosenblum also discuss the process of industrial unionization, the amalgamation of the craft unions that had previously represented organized workers in the garment industry.
  There is a great deal of correspondence with local and regional organizers, reflecting the ACWA's aggressive organizing campaign, undertaken after the formation of the new union in 1914. Organizing efforts in Chicago, New York, Montreal, Philadelphia, and Baltimore, among other cities, are well-documented. Of particular interest is the Baltimore campaign, in which the union battled not only garment manufacturers, but also the Industrial Workers of the World and the United Garment Workers. Letters from August Bellanca, Dorothy Jacobs Bellanca, and Hyman Blumberg document the Baltimore campaign.
  Another subject well-represented in this collection is arbitration. Correspondence between Hillman and John E. Williams, the arbitrator at Hart, Schaffner and Marx, highlights the mechanics of the arbitration process that the ACWA introduced into its contracts. The arbitration experience served the union well in its dealings with the Wilson administration's War Labor Board which was charged with keeping labor peace during World War I. Correspondence between Hillman, the Labor Board, and the War Dept. describes the processes that brought labor peace to the garment industry during the war, and that concomitantly increased recognition for the ACWA.
  Additional topics covered include union organizing in the U.S. and Canada; anti-Semitism in the men's garment industry; ethnic relations within the ACWA in the U.S. and Canada; the ACWA's role in the production of uniforms for the military during World War I; strikes and other labor disputes in the men's garment industry; wartime labor policy in the U.S.; women in the union; and working conditions.
  Notable individuals represented in the collection include: Clarence Darrow; Felix Frankfurter; J.B.S. Hardman; Bessie Hillman; Louis Hollander; Horace M. Kallen; Fiorello LaGuardia; A. J. Muste; and Joseph Schaffner. Major organizations represented include: local unions and joint boards of the ACWA; the American Clothing Manufacturers Association of New York; Hart, Schaffner, and Marx; Hickey Freeman and Company; the Journeymen Tailors Union; Kuppenheimer and Company; the National Consumers League; the Plumb Plan League, and the U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations.
  - Abelson, Paul (Arbitrator, NYC) 1914-18, United Garment Workers' (UGW) agreement with the American Clothiers Association; organizing the Bush Terminal shop. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abramovitz, Bessie, 1914-15, Leadership of UGW faction; "trouble with Hart, Schaffner & Marx;" 8 hour workday for Illinois women; Bessie blackballed by Women's Trade Union League (WTUL) convention as a seceder. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Addams, Jane, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Albert, S. (Secretary, Boston Joint Board) 1920 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Agnell, Paul (Amalgamated Metal Workers) 1923 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alfred, Decker and Cohn, 1919-25 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - All American Farmer-Labor Cooperative Commission, 1920, Sidney Hillman accepts position on executive committee. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1925-27, Arrangement with Prom Bank. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Clothing Manufacturers Association of New York, 1915-19, Preliminaries to the New York City Lockout, January 1916 (wages, hours, working conditions); impact of technology on work; 44 hour week demanded by union; substantial contribution to the Jewish War Sufferers Relief Fund; complaints by contractors; bidding for labor-association versus non-association. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Anderson, Mary (Women in Industry Service, U.S. Department of Labor) 1919 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Arone, Paul (Joint Board Shirt and Boys Waist Workers Union) 1920, Difficulty organizing cutters in New York. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Artoni, G. (Organizer, Rochester and Buffalo, N.Y.) 1923-27, Italian workers in Buffalo discontent; open shop; organizing Polish workers; Artoni's resignation. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Associated Boys Clothing Manufacturers of Greater New York, 1916, Schwartz and Jaffee strike. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Barber, Frank, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Barrone, Anderson and Company of Boston, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bassin, Sam (Organizer, Baltimore) 1919 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Batchelder Company of Boston, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bellanca, August (District Council #3, Baltimore) 1916-18, Industrial Workers of the World (IWW) scabbing; organizing cutters; agreements signed. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bellanca, Dorothy Jacobs (District Council #3, Baltimore) 1915-18, The need to organize women workers; Sonneborn strike and settlement; American Federation of Labor's (AFL) attack on "secessionist" union. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bellanca, Frank, 1915, Organizing Lithuanian workers; strike in Fineman's shop; IWW scabbing; prospect of a strike in Rochester. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Bercovitch, Peter (Attorney, Montreal) 1917 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Bernheimer, Charles, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bisno, Beatrice, 1923-27 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Black, William (Organizer, Los Angeles) 1920, Description of a strike and lockout involving the J.T.U of A., Local 81 and contract shop workers, as well as a request for a charter. Includes men's and women's wage differential. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Block, S. John (Attorney, New York) 1920, Harry A. Gordon perjury case. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Blugerman, J. (Toronto Joint Board) 1920 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Blumberg, Hyman (District Council #3, Baltimore) 1915-25, Cutters' strike in Baltimore; economic effects of World War I (army uniform contracts, women workers, lower wages); jurisdictional question involving UGW and ACWA cutters. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Blume, J. (Boston Joint Board) 1920 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bograchov, S. (Moscow, U.S.S.R.) 1915, Export of raw materials and machinery to Russia. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bongiovanni, J.R. (Organizer, Utica, N.Y.) 1919 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Brais, Eugene (Tailors' Industrial Union) 1914-15, Tailors' Industrial Union joins ACWA; general information relating to situations in Chicago, the northeastern Unites States and Canada. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Brewer, D. Chauncey (U.S. War Dept.) 1918, Foreign speaking soldiers and draftees. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Bulletin Publishing Company (Butte, Montana) 1920 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Bureau of Industrial Research. Inter-Church World Movement, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bushel, Hyman, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Businessmen's National Tax Committee, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Business Personnel, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Buzan, Fred (Knights of Pythias) 1920 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Cahn, William (Progress Tailoring Company) 1925 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Calder, William (Senator from New York) 1922, The wool industry and pending tariff bill. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Campbell, Agnes (Federated Council of Churches) 1925 (Box 1, Folder 41)